Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Nine-Man Arrangements, II.
  - Medley-521 (Box 35, Folder 521)
  - Medley-521 (a) Dancing in the Dark (Box 35, Folder 521)
  - Medley-521 (b) I Could Write a Book (Box 35, Folder 521)
  - Medley-521 (c) Kiss in the Shadow (Box 35, Folder 521)
  - Medley-524 (Box 35, Folder 524)
  - Medley-524 (a) Moonlight in Vermont (Box 35, Folder 524)
  - Medley-524 (b) Penthouse Serenade (Box 35, Folder 524)
  - Medley-524 (c) Stardust (Box 35, Folder 524)
  - Medley-525 (Box 35, Folder 525)
  - Medley-525 (a) Godnight Sweetheart (Box 35, Folder 525)
  - Medley-525 (b) See You in My Dreams (Box 35, Folder 525)
  - Medley-526 (Box 35, Folder 526)
  - Medley-526 (a) Body and Soul (Box 35, Folder 526)
  - Medley-526 (b) Stardust (Box 35, Folder 526)
  - Medley-526 (c) Tenderly (Box 35, Folder 526)
  - Medley-527 (Box 35, Folder 527)
  - Medley-527 (a) I Can Dream (Box 35, Folder 527)
  - Medley-527 (b) Small Hotel (Box 35, Folder 527)
  - Medley-527 (c) I Stepped Out of a Dream (Box 35, Folder 527)
  - Medley-529 (Box 35, Folder 529)
  - Medley-529 (a) All the Things You Are (Box 35, Folder 529)
  - Medley-529 (b) April in Paris (Box 35, Folder 529)
  - Medley-529 (c) You Were Meant for Me (Box 35, Folder 529)
  - Medley-531 (Box 35, Folder 531)
  - Medley-531 (a) Gone with the Wind (Box 35, Folder 531)
  - Medley-531 (b) Sophisticated Lady (Box 35, Folder 531)
  - Medley-532 (Box 35, Folder 532)
  - Medley-532 (a) Careless (Box 35, Folder 532)
  - Medley-532 (b) Does Your Heart Beat for Me (Box 35, Folder 532)
  - Medley-532 (c) Lonesome Old Time (Box 35, Folder 532)
  - Medley-532 (d) Thinking of You (Box 35, Folder 532)
  - Medley-533 (Box 35, Folder 533)
  - Medley-533 (a) Elmer's Tune (Box 35, Folder 533)
  - Medley-533 (b) Remember Me (Box 35, Folder 533)
  - Medley-533 (c) Sam's Song (Box 35, Folder 533)
  - Medley-535 (Box 35, Folder 535)
  - Medley-535 (a) Dream (Box 35, Folder 535)
  - Medley-535 (b) Laura (Box 35, Folder 535)
  - Medley-535 (c) Man with a Horn (Box 35, Folder 535)
  - Medley-536 (Box 35, Folder 536)
  - Medley-536 (a) Dancing on the Ceiling (Box 35, Folder 536)
  - Medley-536 (b) Blue Champagne (Box 35, Folder 536)
  - Medley-537 (Box 35, Folder 537)
  - Medley-537 (a) Alice Blue Gown (Box 35, Folder 537)
  - Medley-537 (b) Apple Blossom Time (Box 35, Folder 537)
  - Medley-537 (c) For You (Box 35, Folder 537)
  - Medley-539 (Box 35, Folder 539)
  - Medley-539 (a) Ain't She Sweet (Box 35, Folder 539)
  - Medley-539 (b) Sit Right Down (Box 35, Folder 539)
  - Medley-539 (c) Smiles (Box 35, Folder 539)
  - Medley-546 (Box 35, Folder 546)
  - Medley-546 (a) Dream a Little Dream (Box 35, Folder 546)
  - Medley-546 (b) Remember April (Box 35, Folder 546)
  - Medley-547 (Box 35, Folder 547)
  - Medley-547 (a) 3 o'Clock (Box 35, Folder 547)
  - Medley-547 (b) Paradise (Box 35, Folder 547)
  - Medley-547 (c) Wonderful One (Box 35, Folder 547)
  - Medley-548 (Box 35, Folder 548)
  - Medley-548 (a) A Fine Romance (Box 35, Folder 548)
  - Medley-548 (b) Hearts (Box 35, Folder 548)
  - Medley-548 (c) I Cried for You (Box 35, Folder 548)
  - Medley-549 (Box 35, Folder 549)
  - Medley-549 (a) Anniversary Song (Box 35, Folder 549)
  - Medley-549 (b) Anniversary Waltz (Box 35, Folder 549)
  - Medley-551 (Box 35, Folder 551)
  - Medley-551 (a) One Kiss (Box 35, Folder 551)
  - Medley-551 (b) I Wonder Who's Kissing Her Now (Box 35, Folder 551)
  - Medley-551 (c) My Buddy (Box 35, Folder 551)
  - Medley-584 (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-584 (a) Blueberry Hill (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-584 (b) I Can't Stop Loving You (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-584 (c) Earth Angel (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-584 (d) Heartbreak Hotel (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-584 (e) Shake, Rattle, and Roll (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-584 (f) Surfin' USA (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - Medley-587 (Box 36, Folder 587)
  - Medley-587 (a) I'll Be Seeing You (Box 36, Folder 587)
  - Medley-587 (b) It Could Happen to You (Box 36, Folder 587)
  - Medley-588 (Box 36, Folder 588)
  - Medley-588 (a) Sentimental (Box 36, Folder 588)
  - Medley-588 (b) Sentimental (Box 36, Folder 588)
  - Medley-590 (Duke Ellington) (Box 36, Folder 590)
  - Medley-590 (a) Boy Meets Horn (Box 36, Folder 590)
  - Medley-590 (b) Sophisticated Lady (Box 36, Folder 590)
  - Medley-590 (c) Prelude to a Kiss (Box 36, Folder 590)
  - Medley-606 (Harry James) (Box 36, Folder 606)
  - Medley-606 (c) You Made Me Love You (Box 36, Folder 606)
  - Medley-606 (a) Heard That Song Before (Box 36, Folder 606)
  - Medley-606 (b) I Cried For You (Box 36, Folder 606)
  - Medley-622 (Box 36, Folder 622)
  - Medley-622 (a) Beer Barrel (Box 36, Folder 622)
  - Medley-622 (b) Enjoy Yourself (Box 36, Folder 622)
  - Medley-622 (c) Jingle Bells (Box 36, Folder 622)
  - Medley-639 (Box 36, Folder 639)
  - Medley-639 (a) Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas (Box 36, Folder 639)
  - Medley-639 (b) I'll Be Home for Christmas (Box 36, Folder 639)
  - Medley-639 (c) White Christmas (Box 36, Folder 639)
  - Medley-653 (Box 37, Folder 653)
  - Medley-653 (a) Aba Daba (Box 37, Folder 653)
  - Medley-653 (b) Hucklebuck (Box 37, Folder 653)
  - Medley-653 (c) Mamma Loves Papa (Box 37, Folder 653)
  - Medley-676 (Box 37, Folder 676)
  - Medley-676 (a) Orchids (Box 37, Folder 676)
  - Medley-676 (b) Tango of the Roses (Box 37, Folder 676)
  - Medley-683 (Box 37, Folder 683)
  - Medley-683 (a) Blue Moon (Box 37, Folder 683)
  - Medley-683 (b) Serenade in Blue (Box 37, Folder 683)
  - Medley-683 (c) Autumn in New York (Box 37, Folder 683)
  - Medley-695 (Box 37, Folder 695)
  - Medley-695 (a) Ain't She Sweet (Box 37, Folder 695)
  - Medley-695 (b) Sit Right Down (Box 37, Folder 695)
  - Medley-695 (c) Smiles (Box 37, Folder 695)
  - Medley-696 (Box 37, Folder 696)
  - Medley-696 (a) Dancing in the Dark (Box 37, Folder 696)
  - Medley-696 (b) Dancing on the Ceiling (Box 37, Folder 696)
  - Medley-696 (c) I Won't Dance (Box 37, Folder 696)
  - Medley-706 (Box 37, Folder 706)
  - Medley-706 (a) Juke Box Saturday Night (Box 37, Folder 706)
  - Medley-706 (b) Kalamazoo (Box 37, Folder 706)
  - Medley-706 (c) Don't Sit Under the Apple Tree (Box 37, Folder 706)
  - Medley-708 (Box 37, Folder 708)
  - Medley-708 (a) Cecilia (Box 37, Folder 708)
  - Medley-708 (b) Johnson Rag (Box 37, Folder 708)
  - Medley-708 (c) Meloncholy Baby (Box 37, Folder 708)
  - Medley-713 (Box 37, Folder 713)
  - Medley-713 (a) Blue Moon (Box 37, Folder 713)
  - Medley-713 (b) I Never Knew (Box 37, Folder 713)
  - Medley-713 (c) More Than You Know (Box 37, Folder 713)
  - Medley-734 (Box 37, Folder 734)
  - Medley-734 (a) Air Force (Box 37, Folder 713)
  - Medley-734 (b) Anchors Aweigh (Box 37, Folder 734)
  - Medley-734 (c) The Caisson Song (Box 37, Folder 734)
  - Medley-734 (d) Marines (Box 37, Folder 734)
  - Medley-734 (e) Semper Fi (Box 37, Folder 734)
  - Medley-752 (Count Basie) (Box 38, Folder 752)
  - Medley-752 (a) Jumpin' at the Woodside (Box 38, Folder 752)
  - Medley-752 (b) Cute (Box 38, Folder 752)
  - Medley-752 (c) Shiny Stockings (Box 38, Folder 752)
  - Medley-752 (d) April in Paris (Box 38, Folder 752)
  - Medley-756 (Nat Cole) (Box 38, Folder 756)
  - Medley-756 (a) Orange Colored Sky (Box 38, Folder 756)
  - Medley-756 (b) Smile (Box 38, Folder 756)
  - Medley-756 (c) Unforgettable (Box 38, Folder 756)
  - Medley-758 (Cole Porter) (Box 38, Folder 758)
  - Medley-758 (a) You Do Something to Me (Box 38, Folder 758)
  - Medley-758 (b) Anything Goes (Box 38, Folder 758)
  - Medley-758 (c) Just One of Those Things (Box 38, Folder 758)
  - Medley-767 (Box 38, Folder 767)
  - Medley-767 (a) Shine On Harvest Moon (Box 38, Folder 767)
  - Medley-767 (b) Sleepy Time Girl (Box 38, Folder 767)
  - Medley-767 (c) Swinging Down the Lane (Box 38, Folder 767)
  - Medley-774 (Bobby Vinton) (Box 38, Folder 774)
  - Medley-774 (a) Blue Velvet (Box 38, Folder 774)
  - Medley-774 (b) There I Said It (Box 38, Folder 774)
  - Medley-801 (a) Hello Dolly (Box 38, Folder 794)
  - Medley-801 (b) Mack the Knife (Box 38, Folder 801)
  - Medley-801 (c) Mame (Box 38, Folder 801)
  - Medley-805 (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 38, Folder 805)
  - Medley-805 (a) Marie (Box 38, Folder 805)
  - Medley-805 (b) Caravan (Box 38, Folder 805)
  - Medley-805 (c) Song of India (Box 38, Folder 805)
  - Medley-830 (Box 38, Folder 830)
  - Medley-830 (a) Talk of the Town (Box 38, Folder 830)
  - Medley-830 (b) Blanket of Blue (Box 38, Folder 830)
  - Medley-830 (c) Hour of Parting (Box 38, Folder 830)
  - Medley-831 (Box 38, Folder 831)
  - Medley-831 (a) Moon River (Box 38, Folder 831)
  - Medley-831 (b) Shadow of Your Smile (Box 38, Folder 831)
  - Medley-831 (c) Strangers in the Night (Box 38, Folder 831)
  - Medley-977 (Box 39, Folder 977)
  - Medley-977 (a) Beginning to See the Light (Box 39, Folder 977)
  - Medley-977 (b) Easy Livin' (Box 39, Folder 977)
  - Medley-977 (c) How High is the Moon (Box 39, Folder 977)
  - Medley-977 (d) Our Love is Here to Stay (Box 39, Folder 977)
  - Memories of You (Box 32, Folder 170)
  - Mercy, Mercy, Mercy (Box 38, Folder 804)
  - Merengue Universal (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Midnight in Moscow (Box 38, Folder 776)
  - Midnight Sun Never Sets (Box 33, Folder 287)
  - Misirlou (Box 34, Folder 337)
  - Mississippi Mud (Box 33, Folder 293)
  - Misty (Box 34, Folder 429)
  - Misty Blue (Box 32, Folder 150)
  - Moanin' (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - Mona Lisa, Vocal (C) (Box 36, Folder 576)
  - Moonlight Cocktail (Glenn Miller) (Box 39, Folder 878)
  - Moon River, Vocal (G) (Box 36, Folder 618)
  - Moon River, Vocal (C to G) (Box 33, Folder 262)
  - Moon River (Box 36, Folder 597)
  - Moonlight in Vermont (Box 36, Folder 637)
  - Moonlight Serenade (Box 34, Folder 392)
  - Moonlight Serenade (Box 36, Folder 595)
  - More, Vocal (G minor) (Box 36, Folder 457)
  - Most Beautiful Girl, Vocal (F) (Box 33, Folder 211)
  - Moten Swing (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - Mr. Sandman, Vocal (Bb to F) (Box 36, Folder 604)
  - Mrs. Robinson (Box 36, Folder 593)
  - M-Squad (Harry James) (Box 32, Folder 169)
  - Mulliganesque (Box 32, Folder 201)
  - My Favorite Things, Vocal (G) (Box 37, Folder 655)
  - My Funny Valentine, Vocal (Bb) (Box 35, Folder 474)
  - My Girl, Vocal (F) (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - My Honey's Lovin' Arms (Box 38, Folder 785)
  - My Ideal (Box 35, Folder 518)
  - My Kind of Town, Vocal (F) (Box 35, Folder 463)
  - My One and Only Love, Vocal (Bb) (Box 36, Folder 628)
  - My Prayer, Vocal (C) (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - My Reverie (Claude Debussy) (Box 36, Folder 610)
  - My Silent Love (Box 38, Folder 842)
  - My Way, Vocals (Ab, Bb) (Box 35, Folder 458)
  - My Way, Vocal (C) (Box 39, Folder 866)
  - Near You (Box 33, Folder 261)
  - Nearness of You (Box 33, Folder 247)
  - Nearness of You, Vocal (Eb) (Box 37, Folder 668)
  - Negra Consentida (Box 33, Folder 326)
  - Never on Sunday (Box 34, Folder 340)
  - New Kind of Love (Box 34, Folder 391)
  - New York, New York, Vocal (Bb) (Box 35, Folder 462)
  - New York, New York (Box 37, Folder 726)
  - Next 100 Years (Al Martino), Vocal (C to Db) (Box 36, Folder 636)
  - Nice 'N Easy, Vocal (C) (Box 37, Folder 465)
  - Nice to Come Home to (Box 34, Folder 425)
  - Night Life (Box 39, Folder 884)
  - Night and Day (Box 37, Folder 729)
  - Night and Day, Vocal (C) (Box 36, Folder 642)
  - Night Train (Buddy Morrow) (Box 34, Folder 395)
  - No Te Vayas (Box 38, Folder 838)
  - No Dimenticar, Vocal (C) (Box 37, Folder 737)
  - Oh You Beautiful Doll (Box 33, Folder 301)
  - Ol' Man River, Vocal (F) (Box 32, Folder 105)
  - Old Black Magic (Box 38, Folder 755)
  - Old Devil Moon, Vocal (Eb) (Box 35, Folder 469)
  - Old Fashioned Ballroom (Box 32, Folder 205)
  - Old Fashioned Way (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Old Fashioned Way, Vocal (G) (Box 34, Folder 433)
  - Old Time Rock & Roll, Vocal (C) (Box 38, Folder 791)
  - Old Wedding Ring, Vocal (Bb) (Box 37, Folder 741)
  - Ole Sole Mio (Box 37, Folder 730)
  - On a Clear Day, Vocal (F to Eb) (Box 33, Folder 252)
  - On a Clear Day, Vocal (Eb) (Box 37, Folder 650)
  - On Broadway, Vocal (F) (Box 32, Folder 104)
  - On the Alamo (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - On the Hefti Side (Neal Hefti) (Box 32, Folder 143)
  - Once in a Lifetime (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - Once in a While, Vocal (C) (Box 32, Folder 157)
  - One Dozen Roses (Box 33, Folder 254)
  - One for My Baby (Box 37, Folder 692)
  - One Mint Julep (Count Basie) (Box 32, Folder 173)
  - One o'Clock Jump (Count Basie) (Box 32, Folder 133)
  - One on the House (Harry James) (Box 33, Folder 207)
  - Opus de Funk (Woody Herman) (Box 34, Folder 387)
  - Opus One (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 32, Folder 175)
  - Our Love is Here to Stay (Box 32, Folder 102)
  - Our Rhapsody (Box 33, Folder 304)
  - Over the Rainbow, Vocal (Bb) (Box 35, Folder 473)
  - Over the Rainbow (Box 33, Folder 318)
  - P.S. I Love You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 35, Folder 454)
  - Paper Moon (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Paper Moon, Vocal (Db) (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Party's Over (Box 35, Folder 502)
  - Patricia (Box 33, Folder 281)
  - Patricia (Box 34, Folder 347)
  - Peg of My Heart (Box 33, Folder 292)
  - Pennies from Heaven, Vocal (Ab) (Box 32, Folder 160)
  - Pennsylvania 6-5000 (Glenn Miller) (Box 32, Folder 138)
  - Pensitiva (Box 33, Folder 269)
  - People, Vocal (Bb) (Box 33, Folder 294)
  - Perdido (Box 32, Folder 177)
  - Perdido (Box 33, Folder 235)
  - Perfida (Box 37, Folder 732)
  - Phoenix (Box 39, Folder 991)
  - Pick Yourself Up (Box 33, Folder 246)
  - Pink Cadillac, Vocal (Box 36, Folder 577)
  - Pink Panther (Box 33, Folder 288)
  - Please Be Kind (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G to Ab) (Box 35, Folder 446)
  - Please Don't Talk About Me When I'm Gone, Vocal (G) (Box 38, Folder 833)
  - Polka Dots and Moonbeams, Vocal (Eb) (Box 32, Folder 191)
  - Poor Butterfly (Box 35, Folder 475)
  - Poor Butterfly, Vocal (F) (Box 33, Folder 242)
  - Prisoner of Love (Box 37, Folder 721)
  - Proud Mary, Vocal (F) (Box 39, Folder 873)
  - Proud Mary, Vocals (F, G) (Box 37, Folder 715)
  - Put Your Arms Around Me Honey (Box 32, Folder 196)
  - Quando, Quando, Quando (Box 34, Folder 348)
  - Quanto, Quanto, Vocal (Bb) (Box 39, Folder 859)
  - Quick Silver, Vocal Group (Box 33, Folder 286)
  - Quiet Nights of Quiet Stars, Vocal (Eb) (Box 34, Folder 349)
  - Raindrops Keep Falling on My Head (Box 32, Folder 185)
  - Rainy Day (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - Rainy Days and Mondays (Box 38, Folder 824)
  - Rainy Days and Mondays (Box 36, Folder 594)
  - Red Roses for a Blue Lady (Box 33, Folder 249)
  - Relaxin' (Count Basie) (Box 34, Folder 372)
  - Return to Me, Vocal (D) (Box 37, Folder 733)
  - Rock With You (Box 32, Folder 181)
  - Rockhouse (Ray Charles) (Box 32, Folder 143)
  - Rosetta (Box 36, Folder 566)
  - San Antonio Rose (Box 32, Folder 159)
  - San Francisco (Box 37, Folder 740)
  - Satin Doll (Box 34, Folder 369)
  - Satisfaction (Box 34, Folder 352)
  - Say You'll Stay Until Tomorrow (Tom Jones) (Box 38, Folder 812)
  - Second Time Around (Box 37, Folder 710)
  - Sentimental Journey (Les Brown), Vocal (Eb) (Box 32, Folder 168)
  - September in the Rain (Box 38, Folder 766)
  - Sexy Eyes (Dr. Hook) (Box 37, Folder 673)
  - Shadow of Your Smile (Box 38, Folder 821)
  - Shangri-La (Box 38, Folder 750)
  - Shiny Stockings (Count Basie) (Box 34, Folder 381)
  - Shorty George (Count Basie) (Box 36, Folder 613)
  - Should I (Box 33, Folder 209)
  - Shuffle Off to Buffalo (Box 37, Folder 675)
  - Siboney (Box 38, Folder 828)
  - Sincerely, Vocal (Bb) (Box 36, Folder 579)
  - Sing, Sing, Sing (Box 33, Folder 312)
  - Sing You Sinners (Box 34, Folder 419)
  - Sir Duke (Stevie Wonder) (Box 36, Folder 598)
  - Sister Sadie (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - Six Flats Unfurnished (Benny Goodman) (Box 33, Folder 298)
  - Skylark, Vocal (Ab to Bb) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Skyliner (Box 32, Folder 115)
  - Sleepy Time Gal (Box 34, Folder 405)
  - Slow Boat to China (Box 37, Folder 728)
  - Slow Boat to China (Box 32, Folder 125)
  - Smack Dab in the Middle (Box 38, Folder 800)
  - Smoke Gets in Your Eyes (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Smoke on the Water (Box 38, Folder 843)
  - Smoke Rings (Glen Gray) (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - Snowbird (Anne Murray) (Box 35, Folder 488)
  - So in Love, Vocal (Ab) (Box 36, Folder 626)
  - So Nice (Box 35, Folder 499)
  - Softly as in a Morning Sunrise (Artie Shaw) (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Solace (Box 33, Folder 267)
  - Someone to Watch Over Me, Vocals (G or Ab) (Box 33, Folder 291)
  - Somethin' Stupid (Box 32, Folder 182)
  - Somethin' Stupid (Box 33, Folder 225)
  - Something's Gotta Give (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - Somewhere My Love (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Song of India (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 37, Folder 735)
  - Soon (George Gershwin), Vocal (Bb) (Box 36, Folder 608)
  - Sophisticated Lady (Box 36, Folder 631)
  - Sorrento (Box 34, Folder 376)
  - Soul (Quincy Jones) (Box 38, Folder 799)
  - South (The Commanders) (Box 33, Folder 232)
  - South of the Border (Box 36, Folder 565)
  - South of the Border, Vocal (Db) (Box 36, Folder 614)
  - South Rampart Street Parade (Box 32, Folder 190)
  - Southern Fried (Box 32, Folder 184)
  - Southern Nights (Glen Campbell) (Box 32, Folder 110)
  - Spanish Eyes (Box 34, Folder 330)
  - Spanish Flea (Box 36, Folder 580)
  - Speak Softly Love (Box 39, Folder 852)
  - Spinning Wheel, Vocal (G) (Box 37, Folder 725)
  - Splanky (Count Basie) (Box 32, Folder 156)
  - St. Louis Blues (Box 38, Folder 780)
  - Stairway to the Stars (Box 32, Folder 134)
  - Stand by Your Man, Vocal (F) (Box 37, Folder 666)
  - Stardreams (Charlie Spivak) (Box 34, Folder 329)
  - Stardust (Box 32, Folder 100)
  - Stars Fell on Alabama (Box 32, Folder 120)
  - Stayin' Alive (Box 32, Folder 192)
  - Sleepin' Out With My Baby Tonight (Tony Orlando) (Box 36, Folder 607)
  - Stormy Weather, Vocal (D) (Box 32, Folder 112)
  - Straighten Up and Fly Right, Vocal (F) (Box 36, Folder 578)
  - Stranger on the Shore (Box 39, Folder 890)
  - Stranger on the Shore (Box 33, Folder 311)
  - Strangers in the Night, Vocal (C to F) (Box 34, Folder 440)
  - Stray Cat Strut (Box 38, Folder 793)
  - Street of Dreams (Box 33, Folder 296)
  - String of Pearls (Box 36, Folder 602)
  - String of Pearls (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Sugar Blues (Box 33, Folder 256)
  - Summer Wind, Vocal (Eb to F) (Box 36, Folder 553)
  - Summertime (Box 36, Folder 617)
  - Sunday (Box 32, Folder 179)
  - Sunny Side of the Street, Vocal (F) (Box 38, Folder 770)
  - Sunrise Serenade (Glenn Miller) (Box 33, Folder 279)
  - Sway (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - Sweet and Gentle (Box 34, Folder 353)
  - Sweet Caroline (Box 33, Folder 222)
  - Sweet Dreams of You, Vocal (Ab) (Box 37, Folder 667)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown (Count Basie) (Box 37, Folder 717)
  - Sweet Home Chicago, Vocal (C) (Box 39, Folder 874)
  - Swinging Boogie (Box 32, Folder 189)
  - Swinging the Blues (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - S'Wonderful (Box 33, Folder 321)
  - Symphony Sid (Count Basie) (Box 36, Folder 625)
  - Take Five (Dave Brubeck) (Box 37, Folder 731)
  - Taking a Chance on Love (Box 34, Folder 389)
  - Tangerine (Box 32, Folder 204)
  - Tangerine, Vocal (Box 33, Folder 275)
  - Tangerine, Vocal (F) (Box 37, Folder 672)
  - Tango of Roses (Box 32, Folder 154)
  - Tea for Two (Box 34, Folder 343)
  - Tea for Two (Box 34, Folder 341)
  - Teach Me Tonight (Box 34, Folder 376)
  - Tenderly (Box 39, Folder 990)
  - Tennessee Waltz (Box 37, Folder 654)
  - Tennessee Waltz, Vocal (F) (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Tequila (Box 33, Folder 297)
  - That's a Plenty (Box 33, Folder 238)
  - That's Amore (Box 37, Folder 719)
  - The Basie Thing (Box 33, Folder 223)
  - The Beat Goes On (Box 34, Folder 390)
  - The Continental (Box 33, Folder 245)
  - The Continental (Box 34, Folder 411)
  - The House of Blue Light (Box 36, Folder 615)
  - The Hustle (Box 38, Folder 797)
  - The In Crowd (Box 32, Folder 106)
  - The Look of Love (Box 33, Folder 240)
  - The Preacher (Box 34, Folder 371)
  - The Song is You (Box 37, Folder 743)
  - The Stripper (Box 36, Folder 555)
  - The Way We Were (Box 34, Folder 358)
  - The Way You Look Tonight (Box 38, Folder 822)
  - The Way You Look Tonight (Box 39, Folder 870)
  - These Foolish Things (Box 36, Folder 592)
  - They Call the Wind Maria (Box 33, Folder 230)
  - They Can't Take That Away From Me, Vocal (C) (Box 36, Folder 621)
  - Things Ain't What They Used to Be (Box 35, Folder 493)
  - Third Man Theme (Box 33, Folder 322)
  - This Can't Be Love, Vocal (Eb) (Box 34, Folder 370)
  - This Can't Be Love (Box 37, Folder 664)
  - This Could Be the Start of Something Big, Vocal (Bb) (Box 35, Folder 491)
  - This Guy's in Love With You (Box 36, Folder 557)
  - This Masquerade (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - Thou Swell (Box 32, Folder 176)
  - Three Little Words (Box 33, Folder 208)
  - Tico Tico (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Tico Tico (Box 35, Folder 486)
  - Tie a Yellow Ribbon (Box 32, Folder 139)
  - Tijuana Taxi (Box 33, Folder 219)
  - 'Till There Was You (Box 33, Folder 284)
  - To All the Girls I've Loved Before (Box 39, Folder 856)
  - To Each His Own (Box 32, Folder 135)
  - Too Close for Comfort (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Too Close for Comfort (Box 37, Folder 702)
  - Too Fat Polka (Box 36, Folder 567)
  - Too Marvelous for Words (Box 32, Folder 178)
  - Too Much Too Little Too Late (Box 38, Folder 811)
  - Traces (Harry James) (Box 34, Folder 360)
  - Trumpet (Box 34, Folder 354)
  - Tuxedo Junction (Glenn Miller) (Box 32, Folder 113)
  - Twelfth Street Rag (Box 38, Folder 759)
  - Twist and Shout (Box 39, Folder 881)
  - Two o'Clock Jump (Box 32, Folder 116)
  - Two o'Clock Jump (Harry James) (Box 38, Folder 820)
  - Ultra (Harry James) (Box 37, Folder 682)
  - Unchained Melody, Vocal (G) (Box 38, Folder 847)
  - Undecided (Box 36, Folder 609)
  - Unforgettable, Vocal (F) (Box 39, Folder 864)
  - Village Tavern Polka (Box 37, Folder 674)
  - Volare (Box 37, Folder 709)
  - Volare, Vocal (C) (Box 39, Folder 851)
  - Wagon Wheels (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - Walk Don't Run (Box 34, Folder 336)
  - Walk on By (Box 36, Folder 552)
  - Walkin' After Midnight, Vocal (C) (Box 39, Folder 889)
  - Walkin' My Baby Back Home (Box 32, Folder 187)
  - Walkin' My Baby Back Home, Vocal (Db) (Box 35, Folder 466)
  - Walkin' Shoes (Box 34, Folder 361)
  - Walter Winchell (Box 34, Folder 356)
  - Watch What Happens, Vocal (C to Bb) (Box 33, Folder 224)
  - Watermelon Man (Herbie Hancock) (Box 33, Folder 244)
  - Wave (Box 36, Folder 585)
  - We've Only Just Begun (Box 34, Folder 399)
  - What Are You Doing the Rest of Your Life (Box 33, Folder 264)
  - What Kind of Fool Am I (Box 33, Folder 258)
  - What Now My Love (Box 32, Folder 203)
  - What's New (Box 33, Folder 266)
  - When I'm Feeling Kind of Blue (Johnny Hodges) (Box 38, Folder 845)
  - When the Saints Go Marching In, Vocal Band (Box 32, Folder 119)
  - When Your Smiling, Vocal (F) (Box 36, Folder 568)
  - Where is the Love (Box 33, Folder 210)
  - Where or When (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - Where or When (Box 32, Folder 109)
  - Who (Tommy Dorsey), Vocal (A) (Box 36, Folder 623)
  - Who's Sorry Now, Vocals (F, C) (Box 37, Folder 659)
  - Winchester Cathedral (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Wind Beneath My Wings, Vocal (Eb) (Box 38, Folder 848)
  - Wind Beneath My Wings, Vocals (C, G, Eb) (Box 35, Folder 448)
  - Winoweh, Vocals (C, G, Eb) (Box 33, Folder 295)
  - Witchcraft, Vocal (F) (Box 34, Folder 443)
  - Woodchopper's Ball (Woody Herman) (Box 33, Folder 272)
  - Words Get in the Way, Vocal (F) (Box 37, Folder 656)
  - World on a String, Vocal (C) (Box 34, Folder 438)
  - Wrap Your Troubles in Dreams, Vocal (F) (Box 37, Folder 690)
  - Y.M.C.A. (Box 32, Folder 152)
  - Yakety Sax (Box 36, Folder 581)
  - Yardbird Suite (Charlie Parker) (Box 32, Folder 155)
  - Yellow Bird (Box 34, Folder 344)
  - Yes Sir That's My Baby (Box 32, Folder 195)
  - Yesterday (The Beatles) (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Yesterday Once More (Box 32, Folder 137)